(Bernadette:)Well, what if the Hulk picked up Thor
while Thor is holding the hammer?
(Penny:)- Yeah?
- Then by the transitive property...
(Bernadette:)...of picking things up,
Hulk picked up the hammer.
(Amy:)No, Hulk picked up Thor,
Thor picked up the hammer.
(Penny:)Hang on, if I go to a bar and pick
up a guy, and he picks up a girl...
(Penny:)...and then we all leave together,
did I pick up the girl?
(Amy:)Did that ever happen?
Hey, we talking about me
or are we talking about Thor?
(Sheldon:)Well, I say that's the last time
we ever go outside.
(Amy(off):)Look right here,
Red Hulk is picking up Thor's hammer...
...because Thor is touching it.
No, it's because they're in space!
- He's touching the strap.
- The strap is part of the hammer!
(Bernadette(off):)No, it's not!
(Raj:)Are they actually
arguing about comic books?